<resources xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools">
    <string name="app_name">Mario Bros Application</string>
    <string name="start_main">Start</string>
    <string name="exit_main">Exit</string>
    <string name="list_character">Character\´s List</string>
    <string name="skills_character">Skills</string>
    <string name="details_character">Details</string>
    <string name="about">About...</string>
    <string name="text_about">Application developed by Cristian Pérez Arias. Version 1.0.</string>
    <string name="welcome_message" >Welcome to Mario\'s world</string>
    <string name="selected_character">Character %1$s has been selected</string>
    <string name="mario_heading">Mario: Mario is a plumber who spends the day in the world of Mario Bros</string>
    <string name="luigi_heading" >Luigi: Luigi is Mario\'s brother, a plumber, who helps Mario solve his problems</string>
    <string name="peach_heading" >Peach: Princess Peach, is the queen of the mushroom world, Mario\'s lover</string>
    <string name="toad_heading">Toad: is a normal boy who played the harmonica, until King Koopa transformed him into a Goomba, who later saves Princess Daisy</string>
    <string name="yoshi_heading">Yoshi: Anthropomorphic hybrid dinosaur</string>
    <string name="dk_heading">D.K.: Gorilla who has captured the lady Pauline</string>
    <string name="wario_heading" >Wario: Wario was Mario\'s childhood friend and he was his idol. Interested in many things that Mario did, Wario endured a lot of abuse to see how to become like Mario, until he got discouraged with the process and swore revenge.</string>
    <string name="bowser_heading">Bowser: Evil turtle who wants to take control of the Mushroom Kingdom</string>
    <string name="mario_skill">High jump, strength and acrobatic skills, can throw fire with a Fire Flower</string>
    <string name="luigi_skill" >Higher jump than Mario, ability to run faster, uses a vacuum cleaner to catch ghosts in Luigi\'s Mansion</string>
    <string name="peach_skill">Can float temporarily in the air, expert in parasols and healing hearts</string>
    <string name="toad_skill">High speed and strength, fast in races and helps with resources in the Mushroom Kingdom</string>
    <string name="yoshi_skill">Can throw his tongue to catch enemies, can transform enemies into eggs and use them as projectiles</string>
    <string name="dk_skill">Super strength, ability to climb and hit hard, can throw barrels</string>
    <string name="wario_skill">Super strength, temporary invulnerability when charging, ability to break heavy blocks</string>
    <string name="bowser_skill">Throw fire, great resistance and strength, can create earthquakes when falling</string>
</resources>
